Siva Krishna Karri

Senior Unity3D Developer

Mobile: +91-8639277629 Email: karrishivakrishna@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE:

5+ years of Experience in Unity3D Development / Software Development, with strong Programming and designing skills.

To acquire a challenging and responsible position, to explore strength and potential in a professional organization to meet the employer's expectations.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Working as a Senior Unity3D Ar Developer at Kiksar Technologies Pvt Ltd, Bangalore from December 2018 - December 2020.

Worked as a Senior Unity3D Game Developer at Pixel Games Studio, Hyderabad from August 2017 - December 2018.

Worked as a Senior Unity3D Game Developer at Capital Numbers Infotech Pvt. Ltd, Chennai from January 2017 - July 2017.

Worked as a Unity3D Game Developer at The Red &Black, Visakhapatnam, from September 2014 - January 2017.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Strong knowledge on Programming in C#.
- Strong knowledge on Object-oriented programming.
- Strong knowledge on Arcore face detection Api.
- Strong knowledge on Arcore and Arfoundation.
- Strong knowledge on XZIMG augmented face library Api.
- Basic knowledge on OpenCV face detection Api.
- Have good knowledge in Unity3D UI and implement third-party plugins
- Experience in Optimizing memory and space usage to support older hardware.
- Have knowledge of the basic functionalities of VR technologies.
- Excellent knowledge on Unity3D, including experience with Scripting, animation, and GUI styles.

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Responsible for the Designing, planning, and coding of the applications(iOS & Android) using Unity 3D.
- Programmed Game Play and executed UI, Menus, and functionalities.
- Implemented game features and suggested workflow and game functionalities.
- Implement third-party plugins like Google Ad mob, in-app purchases, and play game services.
- Interact with the senior software programmers and clients to understand the exact nature of programs required for the software.
- Code the program within the systems and conduct test runs. Validate if the test results match with the expected ones.
- Completing programming tasks to schedule.

EDUCATIONAL DETAILS

B.tech (Electronics & Communication Engineering) from JNTU Kakinada in the year 2013

PROJECT DETAILS

Project 1:

Project Name : AR Virtual Try-on for Fashion Retail

Duration : Dec 2018 – Till Now.

Role : Senior Unity3D AR Developer.

Technologies used : Unity3D, Arcore face detection, XZIMG augmented face,C#.Net and Json.

Platforms : Android, iOS and Windows.

Description:

This is a markerless augmented reality app which allows us to provide a virtual try-on experience by embedding the 3D models on you, so you can decide which style suits you the best! We also use cameras to take pictures along with the products that you are trying - you can share these pics to your friends and family and get their feedback as well.

Project 2:

Project Name : Ar MakeUp.

Duration : Feb 2020 – July 2020.

Role : Senior Unity3D AR Developer.

Technologies used : ARcore, AR-Foundation, C#. Net and Json

Description:

This is a realtime AR makeup & selfie camera app which allows you to beautify your face to apply foundation, lipstick, skin tone, eyeliner, kajal, eyebrows and more.

Project 3:

Project Name : Ultimate Bike Stunts 3D 2018.

Duration : March 2018 – Till Now.

Role : Senior Unity3D Game Developer.

Description:

It is a racing game that pits the player against various levels of increasing difficulty.

Project 4:

Project Name : Real Car Driving Simulator 2018.

Duration : November 2017 – January 2017.

Role : Senior Unity3D Game Developer.

Description:

This is a realistic car simulator game, which is to pick up and drop the passengers and avoid any traffic collisions to escape vehicle damage and unlock new exciting levels to test your driving skills.

Project 5:

Project Name : San Andreas American Gangster 3D

Duration : August 2017 – November 2017 Role : Senior Unity3D Game Developer.

Description:

This is an adventurous 3D game. A player is a real San Andreas American Gangster, who is not afraid of anything, aggressive criminals are everywhere. They rob banks and stores.

Project 6:

Project Name : Virtual Interactive Simulation Game

Duration : January 2017 – July 2017. Role : Unity3D Developer.

Description:

This is an On-line Virtual Interactive Simulation Game intended to promote Cultural Competence in caring for a Puerto Rican Patient with Diabetes.

Project 7:

Project Name : Swords & Crowns

Duration : December 2015 – January 2017.

Role : Unity3D Game Developer.

Description:

It is a Hack and slashes mobile game that can be played in a Multiplayer mode. A Player starts the game with an initial character and keep upgrading the character and unlock new upgraded characters.

Project 8:

Project Name : Bowmen 3D

Duration : January 2015 – November 2015

Role : Unity3D Game Developer.

Description:

It is a Single player third person adventurous 3D game. The game play focused on the hero will kill all the enemies who are attacked and save his kingdom.

PERSONAL PROFILE

Name : Siva Krishna Karri

Date of Birth : 10th May 1992

Marital Status : Married

Languages Known : English, Telugu.

Address : Mvp Colony,

Visakhapatnam-530017

.

Declaration

I hereby declare that the particulars furnished above are correct and true to the best of my knowledge.

Date: Place:

(Siva Krishna Karri)